<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Getting Started on git-repo</title>
    <link>http://git-repo.info/en/docs/getting-started/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Getting Started on git-repo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy;{year}, All Rights Reserved</copyright>
    
        <atom:link href="http://git-repo.info/en/docs/getting-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Quick start</title>
        <link>http://git-repo.info/en/docs/getting-started/quickstart/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://git-repo.info/en/docs/getting-started/quickstart/</guid>
        <description>Quick Start Install git-repo You can download git-repo from: https://github.com/alibaba/git-repo-go/releases.
Choose the proper package according to your OS (Linux, Mac, or Windows), and architecture (amd or 386), download and extract the package.
Copy the binary into executable PATH (e.g. /usr/local/bin on Linux or macOS) to complete the installation.
Run git-repo for the first time Run any subcommand of git-repo, will perform some initialization tasks. e.g.:
$ git repo version  Working on a single repository Make sure to setup a remote tracking branch correctly using:</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Installation</title>
        <link>http://git-repo.info/en/docs/getting-started/installation/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://git-repo.info/en/docs/getting-started/installation/</guid>
        <description>Dependence Install git 2.10.0 or above before install/running git-repo.
Download and Install git-repo   Download the latest release of git-repo from: https://github.com/alibaba/git-repo-go/releases.
Choose the proper package according to your OS (Linux, Mac, or Windows) and architecture (amd or 386), download and extract the package.
  Make git-repo executable before install on Linux or macOS:
 $ chmod a+x git-repo    Move git-repo into an executable PATH (e.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Running</title>
        <link>http://git-repo.info/en/docs/getting-started/running/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://git-repo.info/en/docs/getting-started/running/</guid>
        <description>Execute git-repo for the first time git-repo will perform some initialization tasks on the first execution. See: git config extensions. Running any command will trigger the initialization tasks.
$ git repo --version  Note: git-repo will be recognized as git subcommand so that we can execute git repo (without a dash).
Manual for git-repo Show help message of git-repo:
$ git repo -h  or
$ git repo  Show help message of of subcommands of git-repo, see the following examples:</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Upgrade</title>
        <link>http://git-repo.info/en/docs/getting-started/upgrade/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://git-repo.info/en/docs/getting-started/upgrade/</guid>
        <description>Upgrade git-repo Upgrade git-repo to the latest version, using command:
$ git repo upgrade  Will download and install the latest version of git-repo.
If the upgrade process failed because of permissions or other reasons, it would show instruction in the output message. Please follow the instruction for manual upgrade.
$ git repo upgrade Download git-repo: ############################################################ 100% +--------------------------------------------------------------------------------+ | Fail to upgrade. Please copy | | /var/folders/5d/21v9l2z12j/T/git-repo-0.2.0-619707833 | | to | | /usr/bin/git-repo | | by hands | +--------------------------------------------------------------------------------+ Error: upgrade failed  For this case, run the instruction given by the example, e.</description>
      </item>
      
    
  </channel>
</rss>